didyouknowgaming.com 2018-05-13

# Did You Know Gaming? — Privacy Policy

DidYouKnowGaming.com cares about your privacy:

* We will never rent or sell your personally identifiable information to third parties for marketing purposes.

* We will not share your contact information with another user without your consent.

* We will make a reasonable effort to secure your information in our databases with industry-standard technologies.

If we change our privacy policy, we will notify you by sending the changes to you, or publishing the changes on our site.

 **Information Collection**

Comments

We use the Disqus comment system. Although we do not store such information, information linked with the Disqus user’s account will be shown if you choose to comment. This includes the name the user registered a Disqus account under, their chosen avatar, and a link to their Disqus profile.

Notes

We are a tumblr site, and make use of tumblr’s notes system in our site design. If a registered user of tumblr ‘likes’ or ‘reblogs’ an article on DidYouKnowGaming.com, their tumblr account name may be displayed under our articles.

Advertisements

We may include advertisements on DidYouKnowGaming.com for services or products we offer, as well as services and products offered by other companies. These advertisements may target a particular set of users (for example, those who have expressed interest in RPG games might receive more advertisements related to RPGs). We do not provide any personally-identifying information to the advertising servers or agencies that display these advertisements.

Content Submissions

Within every trivia image on our site there is a line that reads “submitted by” followed by a name or alias. This is a mark to credit the user(s) who sent us information. All users names will be added to trivia images automatically unless the user specifies otherwise.

 **Information Use**

Any information that you provide that does not personally identify you (such as usage patterns, information about pages you visit, and so forth) may be used by DidYouKnowGaming.com for any reason, in its sole discretion.

 **Information Sharing**

We will never rent or sell your personally identifiable information to third parties for marketing purposes. 

We may provide aggregate information, such as demographic, psychographic and page viewing preference information to third parties as we deem appropriate. This information will never contain personally-identifying information.

If you have questions or comments about the DidYouKnowGaming.com privacy policy, please feel free to contact us at [admin@didyouknowgaming.com](https://t.umblr.com/redirect?z=mailto%3Aadmin%40didyouknowgaming.com&t=ZjQ1MmM1YjM5ZGEyNWVjNDhkNzcyODc5Zjg0NWMxMGQ3ZGRhYzg2NCxUbU4zdWpESg%3D%3D&p=&m=0).
